Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- F + G Discordant Spectra, KG11365.860 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 36.
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, KG11365.861 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 39.
- Catalog of Plates Classes N, H, L; Peruvian Plates, KG11365.862 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 40.
- Catalog of Plates Classes C, D; Peruvian Plates, KG11365.863 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 41.
- Objects of Interest on Spectrum Plates, KG11365.864 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 42.
- Objects of Interest on Spectrum Plates, KG11365.865 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 45.
- Objects of Interest on South Bache Plates, KG11365.866 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 97.
- Miscellaneous (Ecl, Solar, Etc), KG11365.867 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 49.
- Discussion of Draper Catalog, KG11365.868 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 50.
- Measurement of Spectrum Plates, KG11365.869 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 51.
- Description of Spectrum Measures, KG11365.870 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: [52].
- Discussion of Draper Catalog, KG11365.871 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 53.
- Discussion of Draper Catalog, KG11365.872 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 56.
- Catalog of Chart Plates (I - 8-inch), KG11365.873 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 57.
- Catalog of Chart Plates (I - 8-inch), KG11365.874 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 58.
- Catalog of Chart Plates (B in Peru), KG11365.875 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 59.
- [Measurements], 1892; KG11365.876 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 61.
- [Measurements], 1892 to 1893; KG11365.877 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 62.
- [Measurements], 1893; KG11365.878 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 63.
- [Measurements], 1893; KG11365.879 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 64.
- [Measurements], 1893; KG11365.880 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 65.
- [Measurements], 1893; KG11365.881 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 67.
- [Measurements], 1893; KG11365.882 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 68.
- [Measurements], 1893 to 1894; KG11365.883 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 69.
- [Measurements], 1894 to 1903; KG11365.884 (Box 33)
  Also identified as: 70.
- Description of Spectra Measures Southern Draper Catalogue, KG11365.885 (Box 33)
- Spectra Class C, KG11365.886 (Box 33)
- Description of Spectra Measures Southern Draper Catalogue, 1894 to 1904; KG11365.887 (Box 33)
- Spectra to be confirmed in Catalogue of III Stars, KG11365.888 (Box 33)
- Spectra to be confirmed in Catalogue of III Stars, KG11365.889 (Box 34)
- Stellar Parallax Stars (13"), KG11365.890 (Box 34)
- Spectra to be confirmed in Catalogue of III Stars, KG11365.891 (Box 34)
- Constraints in South Draper Catalog, KG11365.892 (Box 34)
- Reduction of Plates having less than 4 Standard Stars, KG11365.893 (Box 34)
- Notes on Draper Catalog; Accounts of Share-Holders of the Camera, 1892-05-01; KG11365.894 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: [15].
- Measures of Spectral Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1903 to 1904; KG11365.895 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: 81.
- Measures of Spectral Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1903; KG11365.896 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: 82.
- Measures of Spectral Plates (South Draper Catalog), 1903 to 1904; KG11365.897 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: 83.
- Objects of Interest - Bruce Spectrum Plates, 1896 to 1909; KG11365.898 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: 96.
- Objects of Interest - northern, 1898 to 1911; KG11365.899 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: 98.
  See KG11355.866 for volume 97.
- Objects of Interest - South Bache Plates, 1907 to 1911; KG11365.900 (Box 34)
  Also identified as: 99.
- Variables and Halley's Comet, KG11365.901 (Box 34)
  W.S. Franks.
- Colors of 2149 Southern Stars, KG11365.902 (Box 34)
- Variables, KG11365.903 (Box 34)
  B.P.G..
- Variables, 1912 to 1929; KG11365.904 (Box 34)
- Variables, 1900 to 1920; KG11365.905 (Box 34)
- Variables, 1899 to 1927; KG11365.906 (Box 34)
- Spectrophotometry of B + O Stars, KG11365.907 (Box 34)
- New Variables, 1899 to 1919; KG11365.908 (Box 34)
- Color Indices of Long Period Variables, KG11365.909 (Box 35)
- Spectrophotometry of B and Wolf-Rayet Stars, KG11365.910 (Box 35)
- Variable Stars, 1900 to 1927; KG11365.911 (Box 35)
- B Star Observations, 1902; KG11365.912 (Box 35)
  Maude E. Harriman.
- MC Plates taken for Standard magnitude, 1908; KG11365.913 (Box 35)
- Measurement of Variable Stars, 1908; KG11365.914 (Box 35)
  Margaret Harwood.
- Measurement widths of A + B stars, 1922; KG11365.915 (Box 35)
  Marian A. Hawes.
- Assorted Plate Measurements, 1912 to 1918; KG11365.916 (Box 35)
- 5-inch Equatorial, 1918; KG11365.917 (Box 35)
- Variable Stars, 1904 to 1906; KG11365.918 (Box 35)
  Anson S. Leary and Guy Hill.
- Variable Star Observations, 1889 to 1916; KG11365.919 (Box 35)
  E.H..
  E.H. identity uncertain.
- Color correction for telescope objectives, 1878; KG11365.920 (Box 35)
- Assorted Plate Measurements, KG11365.921 (Box 35)
  L. Hofrager.
- Assorted Plate Measurements, 1928 to 1930; KG11365.922 (Box 35)
- Measurements of Plates, Stars, etc., 1895 to 1898; KG11365.923 (Box 35)
  Edward S. King.
- Reductions of Measures, 1899; KG11365.924 (Box 35)
- Notes: Photographic Instruments, 1904 to 1924; KG11365.925 (Box 35)
- Measurements: Distances, Altitudes, Plates, 1901 to 1902; KG11365.926 (Box 35)
- Assorted Plate Measurements, 1902; KG11365.927 (Box 35)
- Color Distance measurements, 1920; KG11365.928 (Box 36)
- Schilt Photometry, 1927 to 1928; KG11365.929 (Box 36)
- Photographic measurement of light, 1897; KG11365.930 (Box 36)
- Computation Book No. 2, 1916; KG11365.931 (Box 36)
- Photogrpahic Magnitudes, Misc, 1914 to 1918; KG11365.932 (Box 36)
  Henrietta S. Leavitt.
- Variables; Observations, 1902 to 1903; KG11365.933 (Box 36)
- Examination of Plates, 1903; KG11365.934 (Box 36)
- Variables, 1903; KG11365.935 (Box 36)
- Phoebe, 1904; KG11365.936 (Box 36)
- Circumpolar variables, 1895 to 1896; KG11365.937 (Box 36)
- Variable Star Observations, 1896; KG11365.938 (Box 36)
- Variable Star Observations, 1896; KG11365.939 (Box 36)
- Variable Star Observations, 1896; KG11365.940 (Box 36)
- Variable Star Observations, 1902; KG11365.941 (Box 36)
- Circumpolar variables, 1902 to 1904; KG11365.942 (Box 36)
- Variable Star Observations, 1904; KG11365.943 (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1904 to 1910; KG11365.944 (Box 36)
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1906 to 1916; KG11365.945 (Box 36)
- Discovery of New Variables, 1907 to 1908; KG11365.946 (Box 36)
- Comparison Stars, 1906 to 1907; KG11365.947 (Box 36)
- Observations of new Variables, 1906 to 1907; KG11365.948 (Box 37)
- Observations of new Variables, 1907 to 1914; KG11365.949 (Box 37)
- Standard Photograph Magnitudes - T plates, 1907 to 1909; KG11365.950 (Box 37)
- Standard Photograph Magnitudes - T plates, 1908 to 1910; KG11365.951 (Box 37)
- Standard Magnitudes, 1909 to 1914; KG11365.952 (Box 37)
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes - South Pole, 1910 to 1912; KG11365.953 (Box 37)
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes - South Pole, 1910; KG11365.954 (Box 37)
- Standard Photographic Magnitudes - South Pole, 1911 to 1914; KG11365.955 (Box 37)
- Miscellaneous Journal, 1911 to 1912; KG11365.956 (Box 37)
- Miscellaneous, 1911 to 1914; KG11365.957 (Box 37)
- Objects looked up by request, 1914 to 1918; KG11365.958 (Box 37)
- Standard Magnitudes, 1914 to 1919; KG11365.959 (Box 37)
- Miscellaneous - Comp. Stars, 1914 to 1916; KG11365.960 (Box 37)
  Also identified as: 37.
- Catalogs Comparison Stars, 1915 to 1919; KG11365.961 (Box 37)
  Also identified as: 38.
- Miscellaneous (Variables), 1915 to 1919; KG11365.962 (Box 37)
- Discovery of New Variables, 1916 to 1920; KG11365.963 (Box 37)
- Miscellaneous (esp. Novae), 1916 to 1920; KG11365.964 (Box 37)
- Standard Magnitudes, 1919 to 1921; KG11365.965 (Box 37)
  Also identified as: 43.
- Miscellaneous (Variables), 1920 to 1921; KG11365.966 (Box 37)
  Also identified as: 44.
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables, 1893 to 1896; KG11365.967 (Box 37)
  Evelyn F. Leland.
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1896; KG11365.968 (Box 38)
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1896; KG11365.969 (Box 38)
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1896 to 1897; KG11365.970 (Box 38)
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables M5, 1897 to 1898; KG11365.971 (Box 38)
- Miscellaneous Observations - Variables W Cen., 1897 to 1898; KG11365.972 (Box 38)
- Measure of Eros (South Pole), 1899 to 1902; KG11365.973 (Box 38)
- Measures, new satellite (Phoebe) of Saturn, Nova Sgr, 1899 to 1906; KG11365.974 (Box 38)
- Measures of M3, etc., 1902 to 1903; KG11365.975 (Box 38)
- Measures of Eros, 1902 to 1904; KG11365.976 (Box 38)
- Search for variables; measures, 1902 to 1903; KG11365.977 (Box 38)
- Search for variables; measures, 1903 to 1904; KG11365.978 (Box 38)
- Search for variables; measures, 1904 to 1907; KG11365.979 (Box 38)
- Search for variables; measures, 1907 to 1909; KG11365.980 (Box 38)
  Also identified as: 31 or 32.
- Search for variables; measures, 1904 to 1910; KG11365.981 (Box 38)
- Scale measures, 1907 to 1910; KG11365.982 (Box 38)
- Scale measures, 1911 to 1912; KG11365.983 (Box 38)
- Scale measures, 1910 to 1912; KG11365.984 (Box 38)
- Scale measures, 1910 to 1911; KG11365.985 (Box 38)
- Scale measures, 1912; KG11365.986 (Box 38)
- Scale measures, 1913 to 1914; KG11365.987 (Box 38)
- Series Reductions, 1913; KG11365.988 (Box 39)
- Observing Book - M5, 1913; KG11365.989 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions, 1913; KG11365.990 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions, 1913 to 1914; KG11365.991 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions and M5 variables, 1914 to 1915; KG11365.992 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions, 1913 to 1914; KG11365.993 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions, 1913 to 1915; KG11365.994 (Box 39)
  Also identified as: 46.
- Series Reductions, 1914 to 1915; KG11365.995 (Box 39)
  Also identified as: 47.
- Series Reductions, 1914 to 1915; KG11365.996 (Box 39)
  Also identified as: 48.
- Series Reductions, 1915 to 1917; KG11365.997 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions, 1915 to 1917; KG11365.998 (Box 39)
- Series Reductions, 1915 to 1917; KG11365.999 (Box 39)
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1917; KG11366.000 (Box 39)
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.001 (Box 39)
  Also identified as: 52.
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.002 (Box 39)
  Also identified as: 54.
- Measures of Variables in M15, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.003 (Box 39)
  Also identified as: 55.
- Observing Book, 1918; KG11366.004 (Box 39)
- Observing Book, 1918; KG11366.005 (Box 39)
- Long Exposure H.S. Regions and Series, 1918 to 1919; KG11366.006 (Box 39)
- New Satellite of Saturn and North Polar Sequence, 1904 to 1911; KG11366.007 (Box 39)
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1918 to 1919; KG11366.008 (Box 40)
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1919; KG11366.009 (Box 40)
  Also identified as: 60.
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1919 to 1920; KG11366.010 (Box 40)
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1919 to 1920; KG11366.011 (Box 40)
- M Determinations - North Pole Plates, 1920; KG11366.012 (Box 40)
- MF Series, 1920; KG11366.013 (Box 40)
- MF Series, 1920 to 1921; KG11366.014 (Box 40)
- MC and A Plates, 1921; KG11366.015 (Box 40)
  Also identified as: 66.
- Large Magellanic Cloud, 1921; KG11366.016 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1921 to 1922; KG11366.017 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1915 to 1916; KG11366.018 (Box 40)
  H.S. Locke.
- MC Plates, 1915 to 1916; KG11366.019 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1916; KG11366.020 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1916 to 1918; KG11366.021 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.022 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1917; KG11366.023 (Box 40)
- Miscellaneous Plates, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.024 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.025 (Box 40)
- MC Plates, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.026 (Box 40)
- B and MC Plates, 1917 to 1919; KG11366.027 (Box 40)
- Observing Book, 1910 to 1919; KG11366.028 (Box 41)
  Johanna C.S. Mackie.
- Observing Book (Scale Measures), 1913 to 1918; KG11366.029 (Box 41)
- Observing Book (MD Plates), 1913 to 1919; KG11366.030 (Box 41)
- Observing Book (Miscllaneous Plates), 1918 to 1919; KG11366.031 (Box 41)
- B Series, 1919; KG11366.032 (Box 41)
- Observing Book (B Series), 1919; KG11366.033 (Box 41)
- Observing Book (Miscellaneous Measures), 1919 to 1920; KG11366.034 (Box 41)
  M.K..
  M.K. identity uncertain.
- Novae(Maps of S, AC Plates), 1919 to 1920; KG11366.035 (Box 41)
  Title and M.K. identity uncertain.
- Observing Book - Variable Stars, 1912 to 1913; KG11366.036 (Box 41)
  Genevieve F. Matthews.
- Observing Book - Scale Measures, 1913; KG11366.037 (Box 41)
- Observing Book Series Measures, 1913 to 1916; KG11366.038 (Box 41)
- Observing Book - Series, etc., 1914; KG11366.039 (Box 41)
- Observing Book Miscellaneous, 1914 to 1915; KG11366.040 (Box 41)
- Circumpolar variables, 1914 to 1915; KG11366.041 (Box 41)
- Circumpolar variables, 1914 to 1915; KG11366.042 (Box 41)
- Series Measures (principally blue plates), 1915; KG11366.043 (Box 41)
- Series Measures (principally yellow plates), 1915 to 1916; KG11366.044 (Box 41)
- Circumpolar variables, 1914 to 1916; KG11366.045 (Box 41)
- Circumpolar variables (estimate of brightness), 1915 to 1916; KG11366.046 (Box 41)
- Circumpolar variables (overflow), 1915; KG11366.047 (Box 41)
- Circumpolar variables, 1916; KG11366.048 (Box 42)
- Circumpolar variables (record of observations on photographs), 1916; KG11366.049 (Box 42)
- Tables of Ursae Majoris, 1894 to 1896; KG11366.050 (Box 42)
  Antonia C. Maury.
- Rotation of Primary Star and Separation of Satellites, 1928 to 1932; KG11366.051 (Box 42)
- Formulae for reduction, Phase in HA84, 1918 to 1922; KG11366.052 (Box 42)
- Beta Lyras and others (loose papers), 1933; KG11366.053 (Box 42)
- Observation Book, Measurement of Variables and Standard Sequence, 1912; KG11366.054 (Box 42)
  Mollie E. O'Reilly.
- Miscellaneous Observations, Variables, Etc., 1914 to 1917; KG11366.055 (Box 42)
- Scale Measurements of Standard Regions on I series, 1913 to 1914; KG11366.056 (Box 42)
- Circumpolar variables - measurements of comp stars, 1914; KG11366.057 (Box 42)
- MC Plates, 1914; KG11366.058 (Box 42)
- Measurements of Miscellaneous Plates, 1914; KG11366.059 (Box 42)
- Measurements of Miscellaneous Plates, 1914; KG11366.060 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914; KG11366.061 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914; KG11366.062 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914 to 1915; KG11366.063 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1914 to 1915; KG11366.064 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915 to 1917; KG11366.065 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; KG11366.066 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; KG11366.067 (Box 42)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; KG11366.068 (Box 43)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915; KG11366.069 (Box 43)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1915 to 1916; KG11366.070 (Box 43)
- Southern and AS Plates, 1915 to 1916; KG11366.071 (Box 43)
- MC and Misc Plates, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.072 (Box 43)
- Miscellaneous, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.073 (Box 43)
- Obseravtion Book, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.074 (Box 43)
- Southern plates, 1916; KG11366.075 (Box 43)
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1916; KG11366.076 (Box 43)
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1916 to 1917; KG11366.077 (Box 43)
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1917; KG11366.078 (Box 43)
- Mostly Southern Regions, 1917; KG11366.079 (Box 43)
- Miscellaneous, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.080 (Box 43)
- Miscellaneous, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.081 (Box 43)
- Obseravtion Book, 1918; KG11366.082 (Box 43)
- Scale measures, 1918; KG11366.083 (Box 43)
- B Series, 1918; KG11366.084 (Box 43)
- Catalogue of Sc. Measures, 1918; KG11366.085 (Box 43)
- For Catalogue, 1 degree Square, 1918; KG11366.086 (Box 43)
- Cat 4 degree Square, 1918; KG11366.087 (Box 43)
- 8-inch Polar Equatorial, 1910 to 1912; KG11366.088 (Box 44)
  Philip G. O'Reilly.
- 8-inch Polar Equatorial, 1912 to 1913; KG11366.089 (Box 44)
- 8-inch Polar Equatorial (variables), 1913; KG11366.090 (Box 44)
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.091 (Box 44)
  Cecilia H. Payne.
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.092 (Box 44)
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.093 (Box 44)
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.094 (Box 44)
- Wavelength Calculations, KG11366.095 (Box 44)
- Aperture of MC plates, KG11366.096 (Box 44)
- Emission lines, Apertured Spectra, KG11366.097 (Box 44)
- Apertured Arcturus, Vega, 1926; KG11366.098 (Box 44)
  Date uncertain.
- Microphotometer, General, KG11366.099 (Box 44)
- Apertured Altair, Betelgeuse, KG11366.100 (Box 44)
- Apertured c Stars and Others, KG11366.101 (Box 44)
- Single Spectra (Capella, Rigel, Sirius, Altair), KG11366.102 (Box 44)
- Apertured beta Cas, KG11366.103 (Box 44)
- General Ledgers, KG11366.104 (Box 44)
- Line Photometry, KG11366.105 (Box 45)
- Gaertner, KG11366.106 (Box 45)
- Line Photometry, KG11366.107 (Box 45)
- Plates, KG11366.108 (Box 45)
- Apertured Mira, alpha Cygnus, alpha Persei, KG11366.109 (Box 45)
- Pleiades Background, KG11366.110 (Box 45)
- Mira, U Ma Summary, KG11366.111 (Box 45)
- K Stars, KG11366.112 (Box 45)
- Angstrom Magnitudes, KG11366.113 (Box 45)
- Schilt Microphotometer, KG11366.114 (Box 45)
- C-Stars, KG11366.115 (Box 45)
- C-Stars, KG11366.116 (Box 45)
- C-Stars, KG11366.117 (Box 45)
- B-Stars, KG11366.118 (Box 45)
- C-Stars, KG11366.119 (Box 45)
- Temperatures, KG11366.120 (Box 45)
- Miscellaneous, KG11366.121 (Box 46)
- Line Areas, KG11366.122 (Box 46)
- Long Dispersion Spectrophotometry, KG11366.123 (Box 46)
- Line Areas, KG11366.124 (Box 46)
- K Stars, KG11366.125 (Box 46)
- Line Countours, O Stars, KG11366.126 (Box 46)
- Mu null of C Stars, KG11366.127 (Box 46)
- Identifications (Sequences), KG11366.127 (Box 46)
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.128 (Box 46)
  Madelen R. Dwyer.
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.129 (Box 46)
  Mary L. Miller.
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.130 (Box 46)
  Helen M. Lewis.
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.131 (Box 46)
  Jenka Mohr.
- Platinum Grating, Cluster Magnitudes, Sequences, KG11366.132 (Box 46)
- Measures by Bond Astronomy Club under C.H. Payne, 1928; KG11366.133 (Box 46)
  C.H. Payne.
- Various Plate measures, KG11366.134 (Box 46)
- Miscellaneous, 1877; KG11366.135 (Box 46)
- Correspondence, KG11366.136 (Box 46)
  E.E. Barnard.
- Progress of Draper Catalog, KG11366.137 (Box 46)
- Miscellaneous, KG11366.138 (Box 46)
- Various Plate measures, 1890 to 1895; KG11366.139 (Box 46)
- Miscellaneous Counts for Annual Report, 1899 to 1900; KG11366.140 (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous Counts for Annual Report, 1908 to 1918; KG11366.141 (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1902 to 1912; KG11366.142 (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous Memoranda, 1888 to 1895; KG11366.143 (Box 47)
- Accident Book, 1905 to 1908; KG11366.144 (Box 47)
- Notebook, KG11366.145 (Box 47)
- Eye Estimate of Stellar Magnitudes - instructions, 1881; KG11366.146 (Box 47)
  J. Smith.
- Plates and Observations, KG11366.147 (Box 47)
- Measure and Miscellaneous, KG11366.148 (Box 47)
- Eyepiece measurements, 1877; KG11366.149 (Box 47)
  Frank Waldo.
- Financial Record and other computations, 1906; KG11366.150 (Box 47)
- Eclipse notebook, 1888 to 1900; KG11366.151 (Box 47)
- Determinations of parallax by photographic means, 1882; KG11366.152 (Box 47)
  William H. Pickering.
- Preparations for observing total eclipse, 1886; KG11366.153 (Box 47)
- Various essays, 1878; KG11366.154 (Box 47)
- Various essays, 1879; KG11366.155 (Box 47)
- Variables and Asteroids, 1914 to 1916; KG11366.156 (Box 47)
  Susan Raymond.
- Eros series measures, Eunomia scale measures, 1916; KG11366.157 (Box 47)
- Circumpolar variables, 1916; KG11366.158 (Box 47)
- Asteroids, 1911 to 1917; KG11366.159 (Box 47)
- Asteroids, Miscellany, 1917; KG11366.160 (Box 47)
- Miscellaneous Observations, 1875 to 1876; KG11366.161 (Box 48)
  William A. Rogers.
- Plates (Nova Aquilae), 1918; KG11366.162 (Box 48)
  Arthur R. Sayer.
- M- Determinations, KG11366.163 (Box 48)
- Variable Star Observations, 1909 to 1910; KG11366.164 (Box 48)
  L.G. Schultz.
- Observations of Nebulae, 1900; KG11366.165 (Box 48)
  Delisle Stewart.
- Plate Measures, 1923; KG11366.166 (Box 48)
  Rufus O. Suter.
- Plate Measures, KG11366.167 (Box 48)
- Observations and calculations - Ecographical position, 1897; KG11366.168 (Box 48)
  Winslow Upton.
- Latitude and Longitude, Arequipa station, 1896; KG11366.169 (Box 48)
- Scale measures - series and chart plates, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.170 (Box 48)
  Mary H. Vann.
- Observations of Novae, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.171 (Box 48)
- Observations of Novae, 1918; KG11366.172 (Box 48)
- Observations of Novae, 1918; KG11366.173 (Box 48)
- Double Star measures, 1876; KG11366.174 (Box 48)
  Leonard Waldo.
- Correspondence, 1896 to 1897; KG11366.175 (Box 48)
- Observations - 6-inch Telescope, 1911 to 1913; KG11366.176 (Box 48)
  Ida E. Woods.
- SS Cygni, 1917; KG11366.177 (Box 48)
- Instructions, etc., 1915; KG11366.178 (Box 48)
- Observations - 6-inch Telescope, 1912 to 1917; KG11366.179 (Box 48)
- Cluster Variables, 1916; KG11366.180 (Box 49)
- Cluster Variables, 1917 to 1918; KG11366.181 (Box 49)
- Cluster Variables, 1919 to 1923; KG11366.182 (Box 49)
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1919; KG11366.183 (Box 49)
- Objects suspected as Novae, 1919; KG11366.184 (Box 49)
- Examination of AM and AC Plates, 1919 to 1920; KG11366.185 (Box 49)
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1920; KG11366.186 (Box 49)
- New Variables, 1920 to 1922; KG11366.187 (Box 49)
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1920; KG11366.188 (Box 49)
- Examination of Northern Regions, 1920; KG11366.189 (Box 49)
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1920; KG11366.190 (Box 49)
- Examination of AM and AC plates, 1920 to 1921; KG11366.191 (Box 49)
- Objects suspected as Novae, 1921; KG11366.192 (Box 49)
- Special Objects, 1922; KG11366.193 (Box 49)
- Examination of Southern Regions, 1922; KG11366.194 (Box 49)
- New Variables, 1922; KG11366.195 (Box 49)
- Special Examination of MC Plates, 1922 to 1923; KG11366.196 (Box 49)
- Nebulae and Asteroids, 1923; KG11366.197 (Box 49)
- Cluster Variables, 1923; KG11366.198 (Box 49)
- Cluster Variables, 1922 to 1923; KG11366.199 (Box 50)
- Special Examination of MC Plates, 1923; KG11366.200 (Box 50)
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1922; KG11366.201 (Box 50)
- Special Examination of MC Plates, 1921 to 1924; KG11366.202 (Box 50)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1925 to 1928; KG11366.203 (Box 50)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1924 to 1925; KG11366.204 (Box 50)
- New Variables, 1924 to 1926; KG11366.205 (Box 50)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1924 to 1925; KG11366.206 (Box 50)
- Cluster Variables, 1927; KG11366.207 (Box 50)
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1925; KG11366.208 (Box 50)
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1902 to 1904; KG11366.209 (Box 50)
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, MC and MF Plates, 1926 to 1930; KG11366.210 (Box 50)
- Interesting Objects, Suspected Variables, 1926; KG11366.211 (Box 50)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1926; KG11366.212 (Box 50)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1926; KG11366.213 (Box 50)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1926; KG11366.214 (Box 50)
- New Variables, 1926; KG11366.215 (Box 50)
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1927 to 1928; KG11366.216 (Box 50)
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1926; KG11366.217 (Box 51)
- Miscellaneous Milky Way Regions, 1926; KG11366.218 (Box 51)
- Objects looked up for outsiders by request, 1926; KG11366.219 (Box 51)
- Cluster Variables, 1927; KG11366.220 (Box 51)
- Examination of Milky Way Regions, 1929; KG11366.221 (Box 51)
- Dr. Gerasimonic, T Pyx, Shapley LPV's, 1927; KG11366.222 (Box 51)
- Spectrophotometry, Schilt Measures, 1931; KG11366.223 (Box 51)
  G. Maulbetsch.
- Spectrophotometry, Schilt Measures, 1931; KG11366.224 (Box 51)
- Spectrophotometry, Schilt Measures, 1932; KG11366.225 (Box 51)
- Variables and Miscellany, 1905; KG11366.226 (Box 51)
  Oliver C. Wendell.
- AB Plates, 1934; KG11366.227 (Box 51)